A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation photographs FA003
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Agriculture Consultants
  - Meeting of Board of Agricultural Consultants 1963
    meeting, conference, people,
  - Meeting of Board of Agricultural Consultants 1964
    board meeting, people, speakers,
  - Documentary Film - Harvest (stills) 1962
    corn, maize, artwork, statues, people, plowing, fieldwork,
- Arts
  - Report on the Recording of American Music
    document, facts, information, book images, covers,
- Environmental Affairs
  - Fellowship Advisory Panel Meeting
    meeting, people,
- Rockefeller Foundation - Archival Exhibits
  - RAC Construction (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Building, construction, archives.
  - RAC Construction (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - RF - Transportation (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - RF Travel Exhibit - "You Can Get There from Here After All..." (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Transportation.
  - Lewis W. Hackett - Illustration of a Manuscript Collection (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Exhibitions, cities.
  - Rockefeller Sanitary Commission for the Eradication of Hookworm Disease (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Hookworm, diseases, indigenous peoples, children.